Are you ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
Aye, aye, Captain!
是啊是啊，队长！
I can't hear you.
我听不到你说话。
Aye, aye, Captain!
是啊是啊，队长！
♪ Oh...
♪ 哦...
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he. ♪
♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的。 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ If nautical nonsense be
something you wish... ♪
♪ 如果航海方面的废话是
你想要的东西...♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish. ♪
♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通。 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ Ready?
SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 准备好了吗？
海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants!
♪ 海绵宝宝！
Captioning sponsored by THE
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
字幕由 THE 赞助
美国教育部
and NICKELODEON
和尼克国际儿童频道
We now return
我们现在返回
to tonight's Creepy-Time
Theaterpresentation
到今晚的恐怖时间
戏剧表演
of "Night of the Robot."
《机器人之夜》。
Hurry, Gary,
the scary robot movie's on.
快点，加里，
恐怖的机器人电影正在上映。
What do you mean
I shouldn't watch this?
你是什么意思
我不应该看这个吗？
Scary movies don't always
freak me out.
恐怖电影并不总是
吓死我了。
What if Mom is a robot?
如果妈妈是机器人怎么办？
What if Uncle Sherm is a robot?
如果谢姆叔叔是机器人怎么办？
What if Gary is a robot?
如果加里是机器人怎么办？
Gary?
加里？
Psst, Gary?
嘘，加​​里？
Gare-bear?
车站熊？
Gary, if you were a robot,
you'd tell me, right?
加里，如果你是一个机器人，
你会告诉我的，对吗？
Oh, I got nothing
to worry about.
哦，我什么都没有
担心。
And now to get
a good night's sleep.
现在要得到
睡个好觉。
Robot! Oh, my gosh!
机器人！哦，天哪！
Huh?
啊？
How about a little music
来点音乐怎么样
to count me money to?
来数我钱去？
And now for the number-one
song in Bikini Bottom,
现在来说说第一名
比基尼泳裤中的歌曲，
"Electric Zoo."
“电动动物园。”
Hey, that's pretty catchy!
嘿，这真是太吸引人了！
♪ Bee-bee-boo-bop,
bee-bee-boo-beep. ♪
♪ 蜜蜂-蜜蜂-boo-bop，
嘟嘟嘟。 ♪
Yeah, that's not bad.
是的，那还不错。
I love this
young people's music.
我喜欢这个
年轻人的音乐。
I surrender!
我投降！
Oh.SQUIDWARD:
SpongeBob!
哦，章鱼哥：
海绵宝宝！
Squidward, why are
you wearing my hat
on your nose?
章鱼哥，为什么
你戴着我的帽子
在你的鼻子上吗？
I'm not; I'm waiting
for number 17's order!
我不是；我在等
17号的订单！
Number 17... Krabby Patty
and a medium beverage.
17 号...蟹黄派蒂
和一杯中杯饮料。
Of course.
当然。
Sorry, Squidward, I'm
not really feeling
myself today.
对不起，章鱼哥，我
不太感觉
今天我自己。
I keep thinking robots
are taking over the world...
我一直在思考机器人
正在接管世界...
Probably because
I watched this movie
大概是因为
我看了这部电影
where robots take over
the world.
机器人接管的地方
世界。
I even asked Gary
if he was a robot.
我什至问过加里
如果他是一个机器人。
Pretty funny, huh?
很有趣，是吧？
Hilarious.
搞笑。
Just deliver the food.
只要把食物送过来就可以了。
There you go.
就这样吧。
Enjoy your...
享受你的...
Say, you're not
a robot, are you?
说吧，你不是
机器人，你是吗？
No. I'm not.
不，我不是。
Well, keep your eyes peeled.
好吧，请擦亮眼睛。
They're everywhere.
他们无处不在。
Back to work!
回去工作吧！
I feel completely recharged.
我感觉自己完全充电了。
That sounds
like Mr. Krabs.
听起来
就像蟹老板一样。
Come on, little buddy,
play it again, please?
来吧，小伙伴，
请再玩一次好吗？
One more time,
再一次，
for me.
为我。
That was strange.
这很奇怪。
Mr. Krabs was talking
to his radio
蟹老板正在讲话
到他的收音机
and he said
he feels "recharged."
他说
他感觉自己“充电了”。
If I didn't know better,
I'd say he was...
如果我不知道的话
我想说他是...
a robot!
一个机器人！
Nah.
不。
Yes, hello.
是的，你好。
I was wondering if you
could play that song again.
我想知道你是否
可以再次播放那首歌。
Hmm, which one, man?
嗯，哪一个，伙计？
The one that goes
"Bee-boo-boo-bop,
boo-boo-beep."
那个走的
“蜜蜂、蜜蜂、蜜蜂、
嘘——嘘——哔。”
No, man, you're thinking of
"Bee-boo-boo-bop, boo-boo-bop."
不，伙计，你在想
“噗噗噗，噗噗噗。”
Bee-bee-boo, boo-boo-bop?
毕毕毕，毕毕毕，毕毕毕毕？
Bee-boo-boo-bop?
蜜蜂-boo-boo-bop？
Boo-boo-bee-bop?
嘘-嘘-比-波普？
Not "Bee-boo-boo-beep"?
不是“哔哔哔”吗？
Bop?
波普？
Beep?!
嘟？！
Boo-boo-bop?!
噗噗噗？！
Oh, my gosh!
哦，天哪！
Why was Mr. Krabs making
all those beeping sounds?
蟹老板为什么要做
所有这些嘟嘟声？
Could it be that he's a robot?
难道他是机器人？
Nah.
不。
Oh, Squidward, it's terrible!
哦，章鱼哥，太可怕了！
Mr. Krabs...
talking to radio...
蟹老板...
与广播交谈...
beeping sounds...
strange dancing...
嘟嘟的声音...
奇怪的舞蹈...
robot!
机器人！
That's great, SpongeBob.
太棒了，海绵宝宝。
Why don't you work
on this problem back
in the kitchen!
你为什么不工作
关于这个问题
在厨房里！
I'm serious, Squidward.
我是认真的，章鱼哥。
Mr. Krabs is a robot.
蟹老板是一个机器人。
And I can prove it, too!
我也可以证明这一点！
How did you...?
你怎么...?
Let's see... in the movie,
让我们看看电影中，
the robots didn't have
a sense of humor;
机器人没有
幽默感；
they couldn't laugh.
他们笑不出来。
Hey, Mr. Krabs!
嘿，蟹老板！
What is it, boy?
这是什么，男孩？
Squidward just told me
a hilarious joke
章鱼哥刚刚告诉我
一个搞笑的笑话
and I thought you
might like to hear it.
我以为你
可能会喜欢听。
Is it true, Squidward?
这是真的吗，章鱼哥？
Is it hilarious?
好笑吗？
Um... yeah, sure.
嗯...是的，当然。
Well, let's hear it, lad.
好吧，让我们听听吧，小伙子。
Okay, here it goes.
好的，就这样吧。
Uh, how'd it go, Squidward?
呃，怎么样，章鱼哥？
It went... um, uh,
let's see, uh...
它去了……嗯，呃，
让我们看看，呃...
Why couldn't the 11-year-old
get into the pirate movie?
为什么11岁的孩子就不能
进入海盗电影？
Why?
为什么？
It was rated "Arr!"
它被评为“啊！”
Arr!
啊！
Because it's...
about... pirates.
因为它是...
关于……海盗。
I'm not paying you to do
stand-up, Mr. Squidward.
我不会付钱给你做
站起来，章鱼哥先生。
Now, get back to work.
现在，回去工作吧。
Not even a chuckle!
连笑声都没有！
See, Squidward?
看到了吗，章鱼哥？
He didn't laugh because
he couldn't laugh
他没有笑，因为
他笑不出来
because he's a robot!
因为他是机器人！
There's a logical explanation
why he didn't laugh, SpongeBob.
有一个合乎逻辑的解释
为什么他不笑，海绵宝宝。
He's obviously heard it before.
他显然以前听过。
The only reason
you think Krabs
is a robot
唯一的原因
你以为蟹蟹
是一个机器人
is because you watched
that stupid movie.
是因为你看了
那部愚蠢的电影。
Now, why don't you...
现在，你为什么不...
Hey, Mr. Krabs!
嘿，蟹老板！
What?
What is it, boy?
什么？
这是什么，男孩？
Squidward's father
never hugged him.
章鱼哥的父亲
从来没有拥抱过他。
Isn't that sad?
这不是很悲伤吗？
Yes, I suppose
that is rather sad.
是的，我想
这是相当可悲的。
But Squidward
can hug himself
during his break.
但是章鱼哥
可以拥抱自己
在他休息期间。
Now, get back to work.
现在，回去工作吧。
Just like the robot in the
movie... he couldn't cry either.
就像里面的机器人一样
电影……他也哭不出来。
SpongeBob,
this is getting ridiculous.
海绵宝宝，
这真是太荒谬了。
I'll have you know
my father loved me very much!
我会让你知道
我的父亲非常爱我！
That's the final test,
Squidward... the love test.
这就是最后的考验了
章鱼哥……爱情测试。
Robots can't love.
机器人不能爱。
Now, wait, SpongeBob...
现在，等等，海绵宝宝……
Hey, Mr. Krabs!
嘿，蟹老板！
What is it, SpongeBob?
这是什么，海绵宝宝？
I just wanted to tell you
that Squidward loves you!
我只是想告诉你
章鱼哥爱你！
Get back to work,
Mr. Squidward.
回去工作吧，
章鱼哥先生。
Squidward?
章鱼哥？
Aw, me radio died.
噢，我的收音机坏了。
Mmm... these batteries still
have a little juice in them.
嗯...这些电池仍然
里面有一点汁液。
I know... I'll give them
to Pearl for Christmas.
我知道...我会给他们
去珍珠岛过圣诞节。
Me hard-boiled egg is ready!
我的水煮蛋就做好了！
I can already taste it.
我已经能尝到了。
Come to Papa!
来爸爸身边吧！
Gotcha!
明白了！
And what good is a hard-boiled
egg without a little salt?
煮熟的有什么好处
鸡蛋不加一点盐可以吗？
Mr. Krabs!
蟹老板！
Oh, my eyes! Aah!
哦，我的眼睛！啊啊！
Mister...
先生...
Will you be quiet?
你会安静吗？
What did these robots
in the movie look like?
这些机器人做了什么
电影里的样子？
They had piercing red eyes,
metal pincers for hands
他们有一双锐利的红色眼睛，
手用金属钳子
and they ran on batteries.
它们靠电池运行。
Okay, so tell me, does Mr. Krabs
look anything like that?!
好吧，请告诉我，蟹老板是吗？
看起来像那样吗？
I'll evacuate
the customers,
you call the Navy.
我会撤离
客户，
你打电话给海军。
Hello, operator,
get me the Navy.
您好，接线员，
给我海军。
Hello, you've reached the Navy's
automated phone service.
您好，您已到达海军
自动电话服务。
Squidward, the robots
are running the Navy!
章鱼哥、机器人
正在管理海军！
Not the Navy!
不是海军！
Everyone, run for your lives!
大家，为自己的生命而奔跑吧！
Robots have taken over
the world!
机器人已经接管了
世界！
Our world!
我们的世界！
What do we do now?
我们现在做什么？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Hey, a nickel!
嘿，五分钱！
SpongeBob!
海绵宝宝！
Sorry.
对不起。
Ah, that's better.
啊，这样好多了。
♪ Bee, boo-boo-bee-boop,
boo-boo-bop... ♪
♪ 蜜蜂，嘘嘘嘘嘘，
呜呜呜……♪
We need to find out
我们需要找出答案
what that robot did with
the real Mr. Krabs, but how?
那个机器人做了什么
真正的蟹老板，但是怎么样呢？
Well, in the movie the hero
teams up with a buddy
嗯，电影里的英雄
与好友组队
and they get the poop
on the robot.
他们得到了便便
在机器人上。
They poop on the robot?
他们在机器人身上拉屎？
Yeah, you know, they get
the straight poop,
是的，你知道，他们得到
笔直的便便，
ask questions, get information.
提出问题，获取信息。
I never thought I'd say this,
我从没想过我会说出这样的话
but, SpongeBob,
let's get that poop!
但是，海绵宝宝，
让我们把粪便弄出来吧！
Oh, hello, boys.
哦，你们好，孩子们。
What can I do for you?
我能为你做什么？
Why did you lock the door?
你为什么锁门？
Why do you have that rope?
你为什么有那根绳子？
Who's watching
the cash register?!
谁在看
收银机？！
SpongeBob! Squidward!
海绵宝宝！章鱼哥！
What's the meaning of this?
这有什么意义呢？
Untie me this instant!
赶紧给我解开！
Shut up.
住口。
Sweet Davy Jones!
可爱的戴维·琼斯！
What the heck is going on?
到底是怎么回事？
I said shut up,
you bucket of bolts!
我说闭嘴，
你这桶螺栓！
I can't take it!
我受不了！
SpongeBob, are you okay?
海绵宝宝，你还好吗？
Oh, Squidward, seeing you
slap Mr. Krabs like that
哦，章鱼哥，见到你了
像那样打蟹老板一巴掌
is just too horrible to watch.
实在是太可怕了。
No, that's
not Mr. Krabs.
不，那是
不是蟹老板。
That's Robot Krabs.
那是机器人螃蟹。
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
And the only way
to deal with these
robot types
并且唯一的办法
来处理这些
机器人类型
is to find out what they know.
就是要找出他们所知道的。
Right.
正确的。
SpongeBob, you
got to ask him
a question first.
海绵宝宝你
得问他
先问个问题。
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
What color is my underwear?
我的内衣是什么颜色的？
SpongeBob,
海绵宝宝，
let me handle this.
让我来处理这件事。
Where's Mr. Krabs?
蟹老板在哪里？
What are you talking about?
你在说什么？
I'm Mr. Krabs.
我是蟹老板。
We can do this
all night if
you want.
我们可以做到这一点
整夜如果
你想要的。
Where's Mr. Krabs?
蟹老板在哪里？
I'm Mr. Krabs.
我是蟹老板。
Where's Mr. Krabs?
蟹老板在哪里？
I'm Mr. Krabs.
我是蟹老板。
Where's Mr. Krabs?
蟹老板在哪里？
I am Mr. Krabs!
我是蟹老板！
I am! I am! I am! I am!
I am! I am! I am!
我是！我是！我是！我是！
我是！我是！我是！
This is one stubborn robot.
这是一个顽固的机器人。
What?!
什么？！
You think I'm a robot?!
你以为我是机器人？！
We don't think;
we know.
我们不认为；
我们知道。
That's the silliest thing
I've ever heard.
这是最愚蠢的事
我曾经听说过。
I am Mr. Krabs!
我是蟹老板！
He's not cracking.
他没有崩溃。
We'll never get it
out of him this way.
我们永远得不到
这样就从他身上出来了。
I got an idea.
我有一个主意。
Keep an eye on him, Squidward.
留意他，章鱼哥。
Don't fall for any
of his robo-tricks.
不要迷恋任何一个
他的机器人技巧。
If Robot Krabs won't tell us
where Mr. Krabs is,
如果蟹蟹机器人不告诉我们
maybe one of his
little robot friends will.
也许是他的其中之一
小机器人朋友们会的。
SpongeBob, uh, that's a blender.
海绵宝宝，呃，那是一个搅拌机。
Yeah, but I saw Mr. Krabs
talking with his radio before.
是的，但我看到了蟹老板
之前用他的收音机说话。
He called it his
"little buddy."
他称其为他的
“小伙伴。”
Oh, really?
哦真的吗？
Put it on the table, SpongeBob.
把它放在桌子上，海绵宝宝。
You're going
to interrogate
my blender?
你要去
审问
我的搅拌机？
You're crazy!
你疯了！
We're just going
to see what your
"little buddy" knows.
我们正要去
看看你的
“小伙伴”知道。
No, wait!
不，等等！
What are you going to do
to me blender?!
你要做什么
给我搅拌机？！
That cost me money!
那花了我钱！
Where's Mr. Krabs?
蟹老板在哪里？
Not talking, eh?
不说话，嗯？
No! That cost me $24.95!
不！那花了我 24.95 美元！
I guess it didn't know anything.
我猜它什么都不知道。
Go get the toaster.
去拿烤面包机。
No, not me toaster.
不，不是我的烤面包机。
That cost me $32.50!
那花了我 32.50 美元！
$62.67!
62.67 美元！
Fort...
堡...
Well, actually,
that one was a gift.
嗯，实际上，
那是一份礼物。
No!
不！
This is the last robot,
Squidward.
这是最后一个机器人，
章鱼哥。
No! Not my cash register!
不！不是我的收银机！
I raised it myself!
我自己养的！
I got it when it was
just a little calculator.
我当时就收到了
只是一个小计算器。
No!
不！
I thought you said
robots can't cry.
我以为你说
机器人不能哭。
I also said they couldn't love.
我还说他们不能爱。
I loved it like it was me own!
我喜欢它，就像它是我自己的一样！
Ah... at least
he's not laughing.
啊……至少
他没有笑。
Oh, I remember the laughs
we used to share...
哦，我记得那些笑声
我们曾经分享...
SpongeBob, how
did that movie
of yours end?
海绵宝宝，怎么样
拍了那部电影
你的结局？
The movie?
电影？
Oh, yeah, the ending was great!
哦，是啊，结局很棒！
Turns out there weren't
any robots after all.
原来没有
毕竟有机器人。
It was just their...
imagination.
这只是他们的...
想象力。
Hey, it's time to feed Gary.
嘿，是时候喂加里了。
Squidward!
章鱼哥！
Gary, the paper's here!
加里，报纸来了！
You can have this, buddy,
你可以拥有这个，伙计，
because all I need is
the "entertainment section."
因为我需要的是
“娱乐区”。
I am a happy sponge!
我是一块快乐的海绵！
I see you got the paper.
我看到你拿到了那张纸。
Oh, hey, Patrick.
哦，嘿，帕特里克。
Well, I better get going.
好吧，我最好走了。
Yep, see you later.
是的，稍后见。
Cheep-cheep-cheep.
吱吱吱。
What did you say?
你说什么？
I didn't say anything.
我什么也没说。
I didn't say anything either.
我也没说什么。
See you later, then.
那么稍后见。
Cheep-cheep-cheep.
吱吱吱。
All right, quit messing with me.
好吧，别再惹我了。
I know you said something.
我知道你说了些什么。
Ah, but it is you
啊，但是是你啊
that is messing with me.
这让我很烦恼。
Cheep-cheep-cheep.
吱吱吱。
That's what's messing with us.
这就是困扰我们的事情。
It's a baby scallop.
这是一个扇贝宝宝。
I'll take care of this.
我会处理这件事。
No, Patrick.
不，帕特里克。
It's totally helpless.
完全是无奈之举。
It looks like
he can't even fly yet.
看起来像
他甚至还不会飞。
Well, what's the matter?
嗯，怎么了？
Is he stupid?
他是傻子吗？
No, Patrick, he's just a baby.
不，帕特里克，他只是个婴儿。
He's all alone
with no one to
take care of him.
他孤身一人
没有人
照顾他。
Well, we can't just
leave him out here.
好吧，我们不能只是
把他留在这儿。
You're right.
你说得对。
Come on, let's
take him into
the pineapple.
来吧，我们
带他进入
菠萝。
Let's see, we need a box
for him to sleep in.
让我们看看，我们需要一个盒子
供他睡觉。
There you go.
就这样吧。
It's the best seat in the house.
这是家里最好的座位。
Let me see.
让我看看。
Hey, it's kind of cute.
嘿，有点可爱。
Uh-oh!
呃-哦！
I think somebody's hungry!
我想有人饿了！
Is it true?
这是真的吗？
Are you hungry?
你饿了吗？
Cheep-cheep-cheep-cheep!
吱吱吱！
I've got just the thing.
我正好有这个东西。
How would you like
a Krabby Patty?
你想要怎样
蟹肉饼？
SpongeBob
SquarePants,
are you crazy?
海绵宝宝
方裤，
你疯了吗？
That's not the right food
这不是正确的食物
for a little fellow like him.
对于像他这样的小人物来说。
Of course not.
当然不是。
I don't know
what I was thinking.
我不知道
我在想什么。
He needs a tiny Krabby Patty.
他需要一个小蟹肉饼。
Bleah!
哎呀！
Huh?
啊？
No one's ever turned down
one of these down before.
没有人曾拒绝过
其中之一之前已被删除。
Let's try a doughnut.
我们来尝尝甜甜圈吧。
French fries?
炸薯条？
Uh-uh.
呃呃。
A doughnut?
甜甜圈？
All we have left
我们只剩下一切
is this apple.
是这个苹果。
Hello, sea creatures!
你好，海洋生物！
I bring you greetings
from Apple World.
我给你带来问候
来自苹果世界。
Of course.
当然。
Scallops love worms.
扇贝喜欢蠕虫。
Huh? Wait!
啊？等待！
We will bury you!
我们会埋葬你的！
Well, you should be good
for the rest...
嗯，你应该很好
对于其余的...
What now?
现在怎么办？
I don't know!
我不知道！
Aw, don't cry!
哎呀，别哭！
Do something, SpongeBob!
做点什么吧，海绵宝宝！
Uh... uh... uh...
呃……呃……呃……
Blah-blah-blah,
look at the funny face!
巴拉巴拉巴拉，
看看那张滑稽的脸！
Doo, doo-doo, doo-doo,
look at the funny face!
看看那张滑稽的脸！
Look at the funny face.
看看那张滑稽的脸。
Wait!
等待！
I think I might
know the problem.
我想我可能
知道问题所在。
Yep, that's it all right.
是的，就这样吧。
Hold on just one second.
请坚持一秒钟。
Here he is, good as new.
他就在这里，完好无损。
How did you know?
你怎么知道的？
How do you think?
你觉得怎么样？
And I been doing it
all by myself
我一直在这样做
全部由我自己
for almost a year.
将近一年了。
Wow, I'm sure glad you're here.
哇，我很高兴你在这里。
I know, good thing
there's two of us.
我知道，好事
我们有两个人。
You know, Patrick,
since this scallop
doesn't have parents,
你知道，帕特里克，
自从这个扇贝
没有父母，
we should raise it ourselves.
我们应该自己提出。
Yeah, at least
till it's old enough
是的，至少
直到它足够老
to be on its own.
靠自己。
Oh, I want to be the mom!
哦，我想当妈妈！
I don't think you can be the mom
because you never wear a shirt.
我不认为你能成为妈妈
因为你从不穿衬衫。
You're right.
你说得对。
If I was a mom, this
would be kind of shocking.
如果我是妈妈，这
会有点令人震惊。
Just call me "Daddy"!
就叫我“爸爸”吧！
It sure is cute
when it's asleep.
确实很可爱
当它睡着的时候。
Yeah.
是的。
Shh!
嘘！
Hey, SpongeBob.
嘿，海绵宝宝。
Yes, Patrick?
是的，帕特里克？
I never thought being a parent
could be this much fun.
我从未想过成为父母
原来可以这么有趣。
Me neither.
我也不。
Well, good night, SpongeBob.
好吧，晚安，海绵宝宝。
Good night, Patrick.
晚安，帕特里克。
Patrick, breakfast is ready!
帕特里克，早餐准备好了！
All right!
好的！
All this parenting stuff
makes me hungry.
所有这些育儿的东西
让我饿了。
Hey, Junior,
how you doing today?
嘿，少年，
你今天怎么样？
SpongeBob?
海绵宝宝？
Yes, Patrick?
是的，帕特里克？
Kid's got a stinky.
孩子身上有臭味。
Could you change him?
你能改变他吗？
My hands are full.
我的手已经满了。
Ahh...
啊...
Wish I could,
but I got to get going.
但愿我可以，
但我得走了。
Going? Where are you going?
去？你要去哪里？
Going to work.
要去上班了。
I'm the dad, remember?
我是爸爸，记得吗？
You mean I have to do
all this baby stuff myself?
你的意思是我必须做
这些婴儿用品都是我自己做的吗？
I'll give you a break tonight
when I get home.
今晚我会让你休息一下
当我回到家时。
Don't you two stop
being adorable.
你们两个别停下来吗
很可爱。
Okay.
好的。
Phew! What a day.
唷！多么美好的一天啊。
Oh, great, you're home.
哦，太好了，你回来了。
Now you can help me
with the baby.
现在你可以帮助我
和宝宝一起。
Aw, gee, SpongeBob, I'd love to,
噢，天啊，海绵宝宝，我很乐意，
but I'm totally beat from work.
但我完全被工作压垮了。
Huh?
啊？
That guy got hit in the head
with a coconut!
那家伙的头被击中了
和一个椰子！
Patrick, what about my break?
帕特里克，我的休息时间怎么样？
Oh, yeah, your break.
哦，是的，你休息一下。
Uh, tomorrow, I promise.
呃，明天，我保证。
Uh, okay, tomorrow.
呃，好吧，明天。
Phew, another tough day.
唷，又是艰难的一天。
Oh, Patrick, I'm so glad you're
home after working all day.
哦，帕特里克，我很高兴你
工作一整天后回家。
I can't wait for my break.
我等不及休息了。
Work was a killer.
工作是一个杀手。
I need my chair.
我需要我的椅子。
Patrick, I really need my...
帕特里克，我真的需要我的...
Tomorrow for sure.
明天肯定。
Patrick?
帕特里克？
I'll get to it eventually...
我最终会做到的...
Uh...?
呃……？
Uh.
呃。
Patrick Star, we need to talk!
帕特里克·斯塔，我们需要谈谈！
Just one more minute...
I got to...
再过一分钟...
我必须...
Don't "one more minute"
me, Mr. Man!
不要“再等一分钟”
我，曼先生！
Hey! I'm missing
the coconut.
嘿！我失踪了
椰子。
You haven't been
helping at all
with Junior!
你还没有去过
完全有帮助
与少年！
We made a commitment
我们做出了承诺
and you're not doing your share!
而你却没有尽自己的一份力！
You never do anything.
你从来不做任何事情。
I changed his diaper.
我给他换了尿布。
Yeah, once.
是的，一次。
He's only this big.
他只有这么大。
How many diapers
can he possibly use?
纸尿裤有多少张
他可能会使用吗？
Hmm?
唔？
Oh, that's not so much.
哦，那不是那么多。
Hmm?
唔？
So?
所以？
Hmm?
唔？
I had no idea!
我不知道！
What kind of father am I?
我是一个什么样的父亲？
I'll make it up to you, buddy.
我会补偿你的，伙计。
I promise.
我保证。
So, what's the plan for today?
那么，今天有什么计划呢？
No more fooling around.
别再胡闹了。
From now on, I'm Superdad!
从现在开始，我就是超级爸爸！
I'll work straight through lunch
so I can get home on time.
我会直接工作到吃午饭
这样我就能准时回家。
So make sure you save
a big old stinky diaper
所以一定要保存
一个又大又臭的旧尿布
for me to change.
为我改变。
And you could take
the night off, pal.
你可以采取
晚上休息，朋友。
Great, so I'll
see you at 6:00.
太好了，那我就
6:00 见。
6:00.
6:00。
Boy, that was some party!
天哪，那是一场聚会！
Oh, hey, SpongeBob.
哦，嘿，海绵宝宝。
Hey, Junior.
嘿，少年。
What?
什么？
What?!
什么？！
Oh, nothing.
哦，没什么。
Oh, what a relief.
哦，真是一种解脱。
For a second,
I thought you
were mad at me.
一瞬间，
我以为你
他们生我的气。
Do you remember
what you said to me
this morning?
你还记得吗
你对我说的话
今天早上？
Something about
root beer, right?
一些关于
根汁啤酒，对吗？
No.
不。
Wait, wait.
等等，等等。
Let me guess.
让我猜一下。
I give up.
我放弃。
Does "You could take
the night off, pal"
是否“你可以采取
晚上休息吧，朋友”
ring a bell?
响铃吗？
Pfft... I don't need this!
噗……我不需要这个！
What?!
什么？！
Where do you think you're going?
你认为你要去哪里？
I'm going back to work.
我要回去工作了。
Work?!
工作？！
He got hit in the head
with two coconuts!
他头部被击中
有两个椰子！
So... this is work?
那么……这是工作吗？
You know, it's not
as easy as it looks.
你知道，这不是
就像看起来一样简单。
Sometimes I got
to move the antenna,
有时我得到
移动天线，
sometimes I lose the remote,
有时我会丢失遥控器
and sometimes my butt
itches real bad!
有时我的屁股
真的很痒！
Oh, you poor, poor thing.
哦，你这个可怜的东西。
By the way, you forgot
your briefcase.
顺便说一句，你忘了
你的公文包。
Oh, so this is the thanks I get
for working overtime?
哦，这就是我得到的感谢
为了加班？
Overtime?!
随着时间的推移？！
There's that stupid noise again!
那愚蠢的声音又来了！
Oh, that's not a stupid noise.
哦，那不是愚蠢的声音。
That's just Junior
about to jump out
that window.
这只是少年
即将跳出
那个窗户。
Oh.
哦。
Junior!
初级！
Here, darling!
在这里，亲爱的！
Here we come, buddy!
我们来了，伙计！
Come to Daddy,
right in the
old pocket.
来到爸爸身边，
就在
旧口袋。
Uh-oh!
呃-哦！
Did you catch him?
你抓住他了吗？
No.
不。
We're bad parents.
我们是坏父母。
Cheep-cheep-cheep.
吱吱吱。
Cheep-cheep-cheep-cheep-cheep.
吱吱吱吱。
Junior?
初级？
He's flying.
他在飞。
I guess he's all grown up.
我想他已经长大了。
Hey, what about Daddy?
嘿，爸爸呢？
That's my boy.
那是我的男孩。
Good-bye.
再见。
Good-bye, Junior.
再见，少年。
Well, Patrick,
he doesn't need
us anymore.
好吧，帕特里克，
他不需要
我们不再了。
This is the hardest part
of every parent's life...
这是最难的部分
每个父母的生活...
I assume.
我认为。
Despite all we've
been through,
it was worth it.
尽管我们已经
经历过，
这是值得的。
Yeah.
是的。
Let's have another.
我们再来一杯吧。
And NICKELODEON
还有尼克罗迪恩
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
标题为
WGBH 媒体访问小组
访问.wgbh.org
标题为
WGBH 媒体访问小组
访问.wgbh.org